Never lose sight of survival
Bird Box is a horror, thriller, drama film directed by Susanne Bier.
Five years after an ominous unseen presence drives most of society to suicide, a
survivor and her two children make a desperate bid to reach safety.
Malorie Hayes, played by Sandra Bullock.
Tom, played by Trevante Rhodes.
Douglas, played by John Malkovich.
Jessica, played by Sarah Paulson.
Cheryl, played by Jacki Weaver.
Lucy, played by Rosa Salazar.
Bird Box is a 2018 American post-apocalyptic horror thriller film
directed by Susanne Bier and written by Eric Heisserer.
Based on the 2014 novel by Josh Malerman, the film stars Sandra Bullock alongside Trevante Rhodes, Jacki Weaver, Rosa Salazar, Danielle
Macdonald, Lil Rel Howery, Tom Hollander, Colson Baker, BD Wong, Pruitt Taylor Vince, Sarah Paulson, and John Malkovich.
The film follows the character Malorie Hayes (Bullock) as she tries to protect herself and two
children from entities that cause people who look at them to kill themselves.
Bird Box had its world premiere at the AFI Fest on November 12, 2018, and began a limited
release on December 14, before streaming worldwide on Netflix on December 21, 2018.
Despite mixed reviews from critics, the film became the most-watched film on
Netflix at the time within 28 days of release, according to Netflix.
A spin-off sequel, Bird Box Barcelona, was released on Netflix on July 14, 2023.
The film explores themes of based on novel or book,
post-apocalyptic future, blindfold, doomsday, survival horror.
The tone is dark and emotional and intense.